SURELY TOMORROW
EMERGENCY
Ji-woo…
Hey, are you awake?
What am I doing here?
Why…
Why did you do that?
Se-yeong, what are you doing here?
Why are we…
Kyeong-do carried you here.
Ji-woo,
I have to go because Dong-won has a fever.
But Kyeong-do is here,
so make sure to get treated, okay?
Sorry, Se-yeong. You should get going.
No need to say sorry.
My head is pounding.
Drop me off here.
Are you sure you can walk?
Yes.
Hey, Seo Ji-woo.
Why would you take pills with alcohol?
What were you thinking?
If it weren't for Se-yeong,
you could've been gone.
Did your decibel rise as you got older?
Fine. Then those pills.
Why did you take them?
Because my mom came by.
And I really don't like her.
She pissed me off.
Our mom is not a good mom.
I didn't take them to die,
so don't overreact.
Overreact?
Sure, I overreacted
and ran with you on my back.
I couldn't sleep.
Not even with the sleeping pill.
So I took another one,
but I still couldn't sleep.
That's what happened.
Is it true?
You did that just because you were drunk?
How many times do I have to say it,
damn Lee Kyeong-do?
I'm already out of energy as it is.
Stop roasting me.
"Damn Lee Kyeong-do," wasting your time.
What the hell did I do that for?
Go.
Fucking lunatic.
Hey.
Overdosing on sleeping pills
after drinking?
You want everyone to know?
Should I write an article?
Now be quiet and listen.
When humans drink alcohol,
they become idiots.
It's okay if you know when to stop.
But some don't know when to stop.
Like Seo Ji-woo and Lee Kyeong-do.
That weed party in 2018,
why do you think you went there?
You don't even smoke. Huh? You got drunk,
and you didn't know where you ended up.
Imagine being a smoker.
Then you would've been in real trouble.
You won't drink when there's no more left.
You were a lunatic not to have realized
how many sleeping pills you were taking.
Do you collect my articles?
What about the gum on the way
to the fashion show? How do you know?
I dare you to buy alcohol again.
I'll come back and throw everything out.
Who are you? Who do you think you are?
What else? It's humanity.
Get out.
Whether I drink or take pills,
mind your own business.
So stop drinking already!
I know it's tough.
I know it best.
Still, you shouldn't drink anymore.
That's, you know, extremely tough.
It's better to make an effort
sooner rather than later. Okay?
Okay. I hear you.
Leave now, will you?
Sleep tight and order some porridge.
You had your stomach pumped, so go easy.
I'm sick of this.
I heard you, so get out.
You're making me sober.
Make sure to order porridge, okay?
SURELY TOMORROW
EPISODE 4
See? I told you it'd look good on you.
SPRING, 2007
Everything looks good on me.
That's true, but I think
this looks particularly good on you.
Kyeong-do,
I got overwhelmed while putting this on.
Because you felt my love?
I felt how much you worked your ass off.
You must've worked your ass off
with all those plates, huh?
Instead of saying "working my ass off,"
I prefer hearing "working hard."
Whatever. Let's go. There's a place to go.
Where?
See? I knew this color
would look perfect on you.
It looks nice.
But if you do this, my gift doesn't shine.
Is this give and take?
Okay, fine. Give and take.
All right. Very good. Yes.
It's 322,000 won.
How would you like to pay?
-I'll pay in full.
-Oh, okay.
Matching outfits.
It matches the color of my dress, right?
APPROVED
Sure.
Here is your card and your receipt.
-I'm home.
-Did you have dinner?
Yeah, I did.
Good job.
Gosh.
I barely made 300,000 won this month.
Wash your feet. They stink.
Okay.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
SENT
Lee Kyeong-do, call me, seriously.
Why are you just standing there?
Do something else.
Kyeong-do, you know
that tree is the most important, right?
Yes.
Hold it tight! It's scary.
Gosh, it's taking all day.
-Will you spend all day on it?
-Okay, okay.
JOO
I'm off to the restroom.
Looks like a break-up.
Is Kyeong-do having a hard time?
This stop is Dobong District Office.
I told you I was going
to your neighborhood.
I know you're tired.
You made the stage today.
-Did it go well?
-Yes.
I'll go see it.
Did I make you wait?
Oh, no. It wasn't so bad.
Okay.
Did you all make the stage together?
Yeah, well, I only do...
what they tell me to do.
Anything funny happened?
Well… no. I was just busy.
Let's eat. I haven't had dinner yet.
There's a good pork cutlet place
over there.
But I want tteokbokki.
Let's have pork cutlet. It's on me
since you've come to my neighborhood.
You love tteokbokki so much.
Let's go.
TTEOKBOKKI
BUNSIK
Why? Is it bad?
No.
I thought you were hungry.
-Do you want the pork cutlet--
-What's up with you?
What?
You know I've always liked tteokbokki.
So we even had it twice a day.
So?
Why are you suddenly insisting
on having pork cutlets we barely eat?
I just thought it'd be a good idea
to try something else.
Because I'm the daughter of JARIM Apparel,
are you suddenly feeling uncomfortable
having bunsik with me, Kyeong-do?
I said I'd meet you in Apgujeong.
-It's too--
-Better than where your school is.
-What I'm saying is--
-What?
Are you trying to match the level?
Kyeong-do. Lee Kyeong-do.
What do you want me to do then?
Don't you think about how I feel?
Everyone around me is like me
and my family.
This is beyond my…
Ji-woo, will you give me
some time to get used to it?
"Get used to it"?
Do you need to get used to seeing someone?
Either I'm too young to know, or...
too poor to know.
Hey, seriously…
Why do you have to be so twisted?
What is wrong with you?
Ji-woo.
Because you're visiting my neighborhood,
I wanted to get you decent pork cutlet.
Why are you so uncomfortable about it?
I like tteokbokki more than pork cutlet.
I've always liked it!
I know that!
But I wanted to get you a pork cutlet!
I've been thinking about it since school.
So I even borrowed...
money from the other guys.
Can't you just eat it? Huh?
And make me proud.
Can't you do that for me?
Damn it.
I'm sorry.
I just don't know what to do.
What's so hard? What's so hard about it?
The shirt you bought me.
You asked me why I don't wear it.
322,000 won.
That's how much my mom makes in a month
from a side job.
You know,
I know that I shouldn't act like this.
But my parents always work so hard,
and that was…
That was natural for me.
But after meeting you,
everything that used to be natural…
feels so different.
I'm sorry.
This isn't your fault, but I…
Sorry.
No, I'm…
I'm sorry.
Kyeong-do, I'm sorry.
For buying you a 322,000 won shirt.
I'm so sorry that I got you that shirt.
Ji-woo, that's…
I never thought about how you'd feel.
I'm really sorry, Kyeong-do.
Let's talk about this later.
I'll go now.
Shit.
Oh, goddamn it.
The call cannot be connected.
Please leave a message…
Ji-woo, is everything all right?
Why can't I get a hold of you?
I'm really sorry.
That's not what I meant.
I should've given it more thought.
Let me see you for a second.
Do you want to meet near your house?
Ji-woo.
Mr. Kim!
Yes, ma'am.
Ji-woo.
I'll... go.
I'll go to New York.
Okay.
Yes, Secretary Yang.
Get ready to send Ji-woo to New York. Yes.
The faster, the better. Okay.
BOARDING PASS
May I have your attention, please?
Flight 611…
Nice, good.
Hey, wait…
Excuse me.
Will you get off the field? Hey!
Go around him.
Kyeong-do, be happy.
I'll be happy too.
LEE KYEONG-DO
NEW MESSAGE
REPORT ON ALCOHOLISM IN 20S AND 30S
ALCOHOLICS PAY TO BUY POISON
Shit.
LEE KYEONG-DO
NEW MESSAGE
1 CAN OF BEER GOT HER SICK
Gosh, is he crazy? Seriously.
A DOCTOR SHARES DANGEROUS SIGNS
DIAGNOSE ALCOHOLISM
SHARE - SEO JI-WOO
What the hell?
Hey!
Get in.
I have to go to work.
There's a bakery open at this hour.
Do you want to go?
I'm late even if I go in now.
That's none of my business.
Shoot…
-You woke up early.
-I couldn't sleep.
I stayed up all night
watching the useful videos you sent me.
What do you want me to do?
Are you saying that I'm an alcoholic?
Is my life doomed?
If you drink that much, you never know.
Hey,
if your mom tells you to study when
you're just about to, would it upset you?
It would.
You plan to lose weight
but your boyfriend tells you to do so,
wouldn't it piss you off?
-It would.
-And yet why are you doing this?
My algorithm gave me
a lot of useful information.
So I thought it'd be helpful
since you're slacking off. Too much?
Then sit down with me and read together
or work out with me.
That's how you show support.
Instead of bombarding me with videos.
Take them off.
What?
Hey, it hurts so much.
Hey, are you okay?
Jeez, she's so cold-hearted.
Wait. I can't do it. I can't.
Gosh, it's so painful.
Hey, are you done?
Then I'll walk this way.
Gosh, you and your temper.
People usually become kind as they age,
but you are… Jeez.
If I really let it out,
it would've been you I stepped on.
Why did I find all that information
until my eyes fell out?
What are you doing?
Washing my feet.
You still have soil there.
Where? Here?
Seriously. Jeez. Hey, come here.
-Hey, here…
-Hey.
Oh, come on.
It's still here. Did you do a somersault
when I didn't see you?
Gosh, hey, the other foot.
-Over here.
-Where?
-Here.
-"Here"? Here too?
Done. Oh, seriously,
you can't even wash your feet?
Jeez.
What are you doing?
Drying my feet.
Man.
Here.
You do it.
Seriously, you're such a handful.
Don't shake it. Wipe with it.
Oh, seriously.
Hop in. You stayed up all night.
You'll doze off and get into an accident.
Sure.
Lee Kyeong-do is such a gentleman.
But what is this conclusion?
You're still leaving?
-Yeah.
-When?
Would you stay if I yell at you?
Don't even think about dragging me
into the company. For whose sake?
Ji-woo.
I told Mom that I know everything.
And that you told me.
I've thought about
why Dad mentioned my shares in his will.
"Seo Ji-woo assumes
the position of director
and the shares shall be transferred
two years later."
He's telling me to defend myself.
To show that I may not be his daughter,
but I can make a big contribution.
So no one should question me.
Nothing was handed to me.
If you know that, why're you running away?
It's his company.
He raised me like his own daughter.
That's more than enough for me.
How would my shares help sell the company?
CEO Seo, who is the major stockholder,
wouldn't budge.
I mean, what's the point?
Don't worry about her shares.
They'll be settled naturally.
What matters is your decision.
I'm discussing with you a very important,
risky matter,
which can't be even discussed
with CEO Seo.
It means that I'm all in.
Now is the time to throw them.
Selling them in a rush
won't get you the right price.
You've explained this to me already
last time.
What I find strange,
is that CEO Seo is working day and night.
They say the clothing business is sinking,
but JARIM Apparel isn't in deficit.
Then why are you saying
we need to sell the company?
And why is now the time
to throw my shares?
CEO Seo Ji-yeon
won't be working for too long.
I'm the only one who knows about this.
Well, now you know it too.
What do you mean?
The owner of the company
will collapse soon.
She's very sick.
Well, she's not telling her family either.
Well, her symptoms will get worse
in less than a year.
What symptoms?
Is she terminal or something?
Alzheimer's. She has dementia.
What about Seo Ji-woo?
I know she has no shares, but she's still
the daughter of the former chairman.
Oh, Executive Director Choi,
don't you know Seo Ji-woo?
She can't do anything productive
except for breathing.
All she thinks about is having fun abroad.
That girl...
You can't call her "that girl."
You sound pretty aggressive.
If I sell the company,
what's in it for me?
MANZAAR. You can take the men's wear.
It's your dream to run your own company.
Sounds good to me.
All right. Let's eat.
Has CEO Seo noticed?
She loves coffee, so she drinks it often.
Anyway, what kind of drugs are these?
She's not responding much.
You don't need to know.
She's sensitive.
Be careful not to get caught.
I need to know
if this would kill her or not.
I'd end up becoming a murderer.
It won't kill her.
Just do your job.
Today's sermon was great.
Exactly.
Thank you. Bye.
-Yes. Bye.
-Be careful. Bye.
Kyeong-do.
Let's go sleep at home, will you? Get up.
Lean on me.
Kyeong-do.
-Let's go home.
-Oh, my gosh. It's cold.
Should we call the police?
Kyeong-do, wake up, will you?
Let's go home with Mommy, yes?
Kyeong-do.
You scared me. You…
Mom, still, when I used to drink a lot,
I never slept elsewhere.
I always slept here.
That is still praiseworthy, right?
How embarrassing. My goodness.
Were you waiting for me?
Were you on night duty?
Yes.
Mom, add a person to your prayer list.
Gosh.
PRAYER NOTE
Name.
Just put it down as my friend.
KYEONG-DO'S FRIEND
What should I pray for?
No, never mind.
There's nothing to pray for.
Mom.
What are you, a kid?
Why do you keep calling me?
Mom, Mom.
Yes?
The thing is,
my friend drinks too much.
But when you take a look at his life,
everything can be an excuse to drink.
He can't stop drinking
because of frustration. I know it well.
Sorry about that time.
But I'm not sure about how to help him.
He's going far away.
Where he doesn't know anyone.
He'll end up drinking more.
I'm worried from the bottom of my heart.
He might die in England.
How was it when you got treated?
Me?
You probably had something in mind.
"If this had happened,
I wouldn't have drank."
"If someone did this for me,
I wouldn't think about drinking."
Didn't you have one?
I did.
Now, it's annoying
that it's not me or Dad.
Seriously, I think you're the funniest mom
among all moms I know.
If I got a promotion for being funny,
I'd be a senior deaconess.
Cheer up, Mom.
Cheer up and look after Ji-woo.
You've never been a true mom to her.
You should do it now.
Hey, you've known everything, but why--
Mom.
I don't care about the choices you made
or the kind of life you lived.
That's between you and Dad.
What upsets me is,
what has Ji-woo done wrong?
Why do you hate her so much?
How come you never pay attention to her?
All I care about
is how to draw your attention to Ji-woo.
How to make you approve of her!
I should've just let her be.
I should've just let her live
the way she wanted.
I should've just let her be back then.
How could you never…
Call me when you leave the hospital.
I'll send Secretary Cha.
JARIM APPAREL
DIRECTOR
KANG MIN-WOO
What is it?
You have a quick delivery.
It doesn't say where it's from.
The delivery man said
he didn't know either.
Okay.
How's the treatment?
I was wondering
why you wanted the drug so secretly.
Why don't you answer your phone?
Kim Doo-jin?
What?
Is it good? You don't share.
Do you want one? It'll wake you up.
Did it wake you up? Come here.
Yes, sir.
Your article has a unique photo.
Where did you find such a sneaky photo?
I searched tenaciously.
It sounds a bit like
you want to chew me up…
I'm not even the department manager.
I just like these.
It's good, right?
You know what is good. Damn.
Yeah. Are you sure about this?
You might get a call from his agency.
It's perfect
for the tax evasion suspicion.
I'm glad you brought it up.
It's only a suspicion.
Sir, I've looked into it already
and an accurate fact check--
Hey, wait. Something's coming.
Something red is approaching us.
That's definitely a threat
from that distance.
Kiss my ass. What, a threat?
The real threat is you
harassing a junior over a photo.
Right, Kim Doo-jin?
You are absolutely correct.
Has it ever hit you in the nose?
No, does this nose look like that to you?
Look how straight it is.
It looks like you had it reconstructed.
It's so stressful, seriously.
Stop stressing out a hardworking junior
and go.
Go where?
The general manager's office.
You're in big trouble.
What's that look on your face?
Is everything okay?
I'm in good condition…
Hey, if you're going to Chicago
despite that competition,
you should look all cheerful and bright.
You're the first to get training abroad
in the Entertainment Team.
Thank you.
Don't say that.
You're going because you deserve it.
I have no power.
Anyway, thanks to you,
Dongwoon Daily has become
the go-to media outlet for actors.
I'm flattered by your compliment.
Hey, I'm not exaggerating. Think about it.
Thanks to your article,
all the unpaid actors got paid,
and that big, malicious company shut down.
Our company is the number one media
that the artists want to use these days.
I guess I did pretty well.
Keep this momentum going, okay?
When you come back after a year,
write another one like that.
-Where's Dong-won?
-At his friend's birthday party.
Hoengseong Korean beef
lost to a bunsik party.
Kids love fried chicken.
Wait, it's gone.
Hey, I barely chewed it, and it's gone.
It really melts.
Gosh, while on a business trip,
you'd stop by Hoengseong
and get beef for us.
Our Jeong-min's growing up.
Kyeong-do, have some. Why are you so down?
You should've texted me ahead
so I wouldn't eat so much for lunch.
Are you complaining
when I get this for you?
Do you know
how bad the weekend traffic is?
Yet I did my best to feed you.
So while you were doing your best,
you could've texted me.
-Don't eat it then.
-Thank you for the food.
Enjoy.
Oh, right. What's your plan
with your house while you're in Chicago?
Why?
Why bother to move out if you leave
only for a year. Why don't you sublet it?
Sublet?
A friend of mine works in Singapore.
And she's coming to Korea for a year.
She's looking for a place to stay,
you could sublet it to her.
A woman would keep the place tidy.
How much would you want?
Hey, someone gets to train abroad for free
and also receive rent.
It's "the poor get poorer
and the rich get richer"?
Don't be silly.
When are you leaving?
I'm not sure yet. Eventually.
Why?
Now that Ji-woo's single,
you don't want to leave?
What are you talking about?
What does she have to do with Chicago?
Right. You should stop getting involved
with Seo Ji-woo.
She's fine on her own.
What do you mean she's fine?
She always gets drunk
and talks about running away.
And she needs to quit drinking.
Besides, there's no one to stop her,
so she'll only end up drinking more.
Admit it.
You don't care about Chicago
because of Seo Ji-woo. Am I right?
No, it's just that
she's having a hard time.
And if she leaves now, her family might…
Well, you don't need to know.
You need to stop!
No need to raise your voice.
Look at what this idiot's doing.
Because of Seo Ji-woo…
I don't care about
how much you love Seo Ji-woo, but we…
we also love you very much, okay?
You asshole.
Why, you...
Did water get you drunk?
Yes, we're drinking water.
With this fine food,
I can't believe we're drinking water.
Do you have any idea…
how much we were worried every single day
because we thought you'd die?
And now you're worried
about Seo Ji-woo drinking, you jackass?
WINTER, 2017
Jeez.
Gosh…
Let's do this for this week.
Okay.
Gosh.
-Wait, no.
-Leave it.
But this is mine.
You want me to get you coffee?
But it's just water.
It's water…
Did you request time off
just to keep drinking?
I can't cause trouble at work.
Hey, I'm glad you brought that up.
What happened to the Culture Team's ace
Lee Kyeong-do?
You worked on the forged painting scandal
for a year and shook up the art scene.
I became an assistant manager
thanks to you.
But why are you drinking alcohol
like water?
Why, Kyeong-do?
Hey, Lee Kyeong-do.
I'm sorry.
Han-kyeong, I'm sorry.
Let's go. You've had enough.
Jeong-min, let's drink.
Let's drink.
No.
-I'll pay for the chauffeur service.
-What?
I'll pay, here. Drink before you go.
Whatever. It's time to go now.
-But it's been a while since we've met.
-Come on. Stop it.
Oh, drink before you go.
Oh, okay. Okay, fine.
Just one bottle.
Only one bottle.
Only one. Okay?
-Kyeong-do.
-Okay?
-Hey…
-What the hell?
Jeez, seriously.
-Hey, I'll do it. Careful.
-Kyeong-do.
Oh, wait. Get up. Jeez.
Oh, seriously. Jeez, come on.
Oh, I'm okay. I'm fine.
Shit.
Man, I fell.
I'll go pay.
Oh, I can get up on my own.
Come to your senses, will you?
-Jesus.
-I can get up.
Kyeong-do!
Kyeong-do.
Kyeong-do, hold, hold onto me.
Kyeong-do, hold onto Mommy.
Oh, stop it!
Your mother got hurt.
Her arm's fractured.
Why?
She fell because her drunk son pushed her.
Jeez.
Kyeong-do.
Mom.
I'll come back after treatment.
Don't worry about us.
Mom.
Yes.
Mom, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Jeong-min.
What are you doing? This is disgusting.
I'm so touched today.
Speaking of which,
I'm full. Can you pack my share?
Se-yeong, do you have a scale?
Give him exactly 600 grams.
Kiss. Kiss.
I'm running an errand. Jeong-min's errand.
You know Jeong-min sells used cars.
He goes around the whole country.
It was Gangwon Province today.
And he bought this in Hoengseong
on his way back. You know?
I know he wouldn't buy enough for me.
Here.
Have a piece.
Are you here to watch me?
That too.
You don't even deny it.
Aren't you eating?
I already did.
I mean, shouldn't the one who ate
wash the dishes?
She has no sense of shame. This should go…
What?
I'm leaving.
I'll keep checking on you.
Don't even think about drinking, got it?
-Are you a gangster?
-I'm a foster carer.
Who asked you to foster me? Who?
The past me?
Wait.
That was so cool.
That's cool. "The past me." Ha.
So it's inefficient to separate the films
from the drama?
Yes, with the variety shows,
it separates into several parts.
Then some artists would overlap.
Then the articles may overlap too.
That's right. I had an interview with
actor Cho Seok-hyun for his drama,
but you ran his variety article first,
remember?
37°16'99.5"N 127°02'33.8"E
7:00 P.M.
Remember, Kyeong-do?
What's that? Latitude and longitude?
So, I think it's better to assign
the artists individually.
Instead of assigning by the type?
Yes, while keeping up with the shows,
we'll have someone in charge of big names.
Right, it's better to assign the work
in a more efficient way.
Okay. That means one person
will be in charge of many.
Intern, who's your favorite?
JUWON UNIVERSITY FIELD
Any idol is fine with me.
Are you kidding me?
Oh, will you stop?
-What?
-Cut it out.
Continue.
Stop what?
Then let's decide on this again
next month.
Hey, block it.
-Over there.
-Pass it to me.
Move forward.
To the left.
You're late.
It's hell to come here during rush hour.
Why did you call me out here?
Honestly,
I wasn't sure about going to England.
Even back then,
I barely plucked up my courage.
When you stopped me,
I pretended to be stopped.
I think it might be better to stay.
But I really have to go now.
Why are you drawing the wrong conclusion?
Because of you.
You made it clear.
It's only right for me to go.
I keep imagining things.
All the things you say,
being sweet in a grumpy way,
your support in your harsh words,
the worried look in your eyes...
I can't stop giving meaning to all that.
I keep picturing myself as Seo Ji-woo
from Juwon University.
I keep coming back here,
but you're not here anymore.
If you stop me again,
that means you're also confused.
SPARKLING WATER
ENERGY DRINK
You just asked me out.
You just called me pretty.
I said you had a pretty-ish face.
I didn't exactly say pretty.
It was to encourage you to stop swearing.
If you say things like that
without meaning them, you're a bastard.
Don't be like that.
You're melting my heart.
I can't fall for you again.
If you stop me again,
that means you're also confused.
It's been a while.
You didn't change the door code?
Why are you so surprised?
Thought I'd still be
in the detention center?
Right…
Let's go outside. Let's talk outside.
Oh, I'm going to leave soon. Yeah.
I was just passing by,
and I thought about you.
Jin-eon,
you're making me feel uncomfortable.
Ji-woo, let's get back together, yes?
Fine. Yeah, I admit that I cheated on you
and gave you a hard time.
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry about that.
I even quit doing drugs. Want to see it?
Once my probation is over,
I'll be working at my father's company.
I'm not even interested in JARIM.
I'm just going to start all over again.
Let's start together, yes?
I'm not interested either.
Oh, Ji-woo. Right, Ji-woo.
Yeah? Ji-woo.
Ji-woo, do you think
you can have this decent life
without me or my family?
Ji-woo, you're…
Oh, you're Cinderella in rags
after midnight. Okay?
Who'd even bat an eye at you? The prince?
You'll only be surrounded by rats.
Okay, Ji-woo?
Hey, if you just leave after saying--
What is this, Ji-woo?
A guest?
I only bought two servings of gimbap.
Ji-woo, are you okay?
Why are you standing there
like a soaked puppy?
You're that man in the picture. Shit.
Don't you think it's a little too late
to have a guest?
It seems you are the guest.
What's going on with luggage at this hour?
What's going on, Ji-woo?
You should look at me.
You were talking to me.
What is going on?
I'm flirting with her.
And I'm doing my best.
SURELY TOMORROW
Jeez.
CLOTHING COLLECTION BOX
Shoot. What the heck? Why is it so deep?
Dad, can you overlock stitch this?
Hey, even your mom wouldn't wear this.
Jeez, throw it out.
Why mend it when it's already gone?
Mom, you've changed.
Being frugal is the key to wealth.
That's not being frugal.
That's pitiful. Throw it out already.
No! This is basically my security blanket.
Your security blanket?
That's crazy.
Then get married! You're getting weird.
Crazy?
I'm going to a different laundromat.
SOMANG LAUNDROMAT
Did I not breastfeed him enough?
How can he have a security blanket
at this age?
Let's sleep together. The bed is big.
If you come here again after work,
you're a dead man.
Are you crazy?
I went all the way there. Was she
flirting with me or threatening me?
Have you done it?
All right. Let's go.
Kyeong-do.
I'll leave when you become
a decent human being. Say no more.
I know this is shameless,
but it's good to be with you.
How long will I be in love with you?